ILR School Office of Student Services Additional Records /4125
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Office of Student Services Additional Records
1951-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Office of Student Services
/4125
14 cubic feet
14 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3107984
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3045: ILR School Announcement Catalogs /4031: ILR School Office of Resident Instruction Sample MILR Examination /4114: ILR School Office of Student Services Additional Records /4140: ILR School Admissions Office Files
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Office of Student Services
3107984
- MILR Comprehensive Exam.. Grading Sheets (Box 1, Folder 1)
- G 394 MS in ILR Exam 5/7/51, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- MILR Comp. Exams: 6/50, 9/50, 10/50, 1/51, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- MS in ILR Comprehensive Examination (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Comprehensive Examination 1/4/52, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- G 904 MS in ILR Exam 9/5/51, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- L 830 MILR Comp. Exam. 7/13/53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- K 364 MILP Comp. Exam. 1/7/53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- L 959 MS in ILR Exam - 5/16/52, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- O-554 - MILR Comp. Exam - 5/28/54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- M 125 MILR Comp. Exam. 12/15/53, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- R-164 MILR Comp. Exam 5/4/55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- P-878 MILR Comp. Exam 12/13/54, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- S-609 MILR Comp. Exam 12/8/55, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- MILR Comp. Exam 3/5/56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 56-1947 MILR Comp. Exam 4/23/56, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- MILR Comprehensive Examination 1/7/57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- MILR Comp. Exam. 5-10-57, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- MILR Comp. Exam. Jan. 8-9-1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - Jan. 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - Jan. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - May 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- MILR Comp. Exam. Jan. 1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - May 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - Jan. 1962 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam. May 1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam. - Jan. 8, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- MILR Comp. Exam. - May 1963 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam - May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam. - Jan. 6, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam - Jan. 4, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- MILR Comprehensive Exam. - Jan. 4-5-, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- MILR Comprehensive Examination--May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- MILR Comprehensive Examination 5/69, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- MILR Comprehensive Examination 5/69, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- One Copy of Each MILR written Exam May 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Envelope
- Extra Sets of MILR Exam papers May 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- MacIntyre or Hawslowe May 1960 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Milk Exam Jan. 1960 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- June 1954 Mail Comp. (Box 2, Folder 7)
- MILR Comp. Exam. Jan. 8-9 1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- MILR Comprehensive Jan. 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- May 1961 MILR Comp. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- MILR Comp. 1-9-62 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- MILR June '62, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- NYSSILR Memorandums, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- MILR Comp. 1-63, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- MILR Comp. March 15, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- May 1963 MILR Comprehensive Examination (Box 2, Folder 16)
- MILR Comp. Jan. 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- May 1964 MILR Comp. (Box 2, Folder 18)
- MILR Comp. May 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- MILR Comp. Exam Jan. 4-5, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Anne Dimock Confidential, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Professor Aronson, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Professor Aronson (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Carceres Hornelt Ricardo '63-'64, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Kondo, Toshiya (Mr.) '63, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Farje, Ricardo R. Fall '61, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Braun, Rudolf Dr. '60, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Said A. Fattah, M. Dr. '60, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Savicevic, Dusan (Mr.) '60, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Visiting Scholars '60-'61, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Visiting Scholars '60-'61, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Soontharabhesaj, Pranee '59, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Evans, Hywel '58-'61, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Seppanen, A. Paavo '58, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Siegenthaler, Dr. Jurg, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Taylor, Graham '57, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Uchida, Tadatashi Prof. '57, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Zaim, S. Dr. '56, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Malisoff, Dusan Dr. '49-'50, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Foreign Students Misc., 1957-1963 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1961 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1961 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1961 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1960 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1960 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Student Body Data, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1958 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1958 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Student Body DataFall Term 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1957 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1956 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1956 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1956 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1956 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1956 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1955 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1954 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1954 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1953 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1953 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1952 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1952 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1952 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1951 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1951 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Student Body Data Spring Term 1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Student Body Data Fall Term 1950 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- MILR Questions and Papers Comprehensive January 1970 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Curriculum - Surveys, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Questionnaires - 1958-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Undergraduate Curriculum, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Curriculum - Reading Lists, 1945-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Curric., 1954 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- C.A. Hanson, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Electives (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Basic Accounting Principles John Courtney Cornell University, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Curriculum - General Correspondence, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Curriculum Revisions, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Orientation Course Outlines, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - Course Offerings 1950-57, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Course Outline ILR 70 Administrative Practices 7 Procedures, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- ILR 72 - Civil Rights in Industrial and Labor Relations, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Course Outline M. Konvitz, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- ILR 240 - The Corporation, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- ILR 293 - Survey of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- ILR 300 - Labor Relations Law and Legislation, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- ILR 393 - Elements of Law, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- ILR 401 - Labor Relations - Selected Problems in Contracts Making and Admin., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- ILR 453 - Political Ideologies and Industries Relations, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- ILR 491 - Public Policy and Industrial and Labor Relations, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- ILR 492 - Comparative Labor Relations, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Methods Research in the Social Sciences - ILR 497, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- ILR 520 - Human Relations in Industry, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- ILR 530 - Industrial Education, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- ILR 590 - Report Writing, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- ILR 621 - Personality Study and Intensive Interviewing, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- ILR 653 - Seminar in Labor Union Admin., 1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- ILR 672 - Seminar - The Aged in American Society, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Advisory Council, 1959-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Memorandum, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ninrichs, John R., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Summer 1962 - Room Requests (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Summer Session - Social Studies, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Summer Session, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Summer Session 1961 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Misc., 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- 1959 Summer Session, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 1958 Summer Session (Box 5, Folder 10)
- ILR, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Report on Institutional Self-Evaluation Submitted in Connection with Accreditation by the Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- New Building (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Appendices to Report on Institutional Self-Evaluation submitted in connection with Accreditation by the Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Bound
- Accreditation, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Cornell University - School of Education, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Budget General 1946-1962 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Budget Estimates-Accessory Instr. '56-'62, 1956-1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- 1956-8 Academic Standards, Committee on, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Academic Standards Com. 1953-55, 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Academic Standards Com. 1946-52, 1946-1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Accreditation, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Arnold Hanson, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Administrative Conference, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Admissions Office 1957-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Admission Statistics 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Admission Statistics 1957-1963 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Advisory Council, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Advisory Council, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Advisory Council Mtg. November 1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Advisory Council Mtg. November 1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Advisory Council Mtg. November 1955 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Advisory Council Mtg. May 1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- American Design Award, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Budget FTE Data, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Business and Professional Women's Club, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Class Ranking - From 1947 to 1959, 1947-1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cornell Parents Weekend - 1956-1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Dean Catherwood - 1947-1953 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Dean McConnell, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Dean's List, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Educational Policy (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Examinations - Conduct of:, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Faculty Meeting (Box 6, Folder 26)
- ILR 500 - Syllabus - 1950 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- ILR 500 - Syllabus - 1950 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- ILR 500 Written Communications, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- ILR Faculty Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- ILR Faculty Meetings Minutes 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- ILR Faculty Meetings Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- ILR Faculty Meetings 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- ILR Faculty Meetings Minutes 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- ILR Faculty Meetings Minutes 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- ILR Faculty Minutes #7 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ILR Faculty Minutes #6 1960-1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Faculty Meeting Fall 1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Faculty Minutes #4 - 1957 to (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Faculty Meeting 1958 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Faculty Minutes-- 3 - 1954-56, 1954-1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Faculty Minutes 2 - 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Faculty Minutes 1 - 1945-1949 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Interviewing of Entering Students - to 1965 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Foreign Students to 1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Foreign Language Requirement Questionnaires, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Lab Frees - 1949-1960 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Military Science and Tactics -- 1952-1963 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- New Building, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Orientation Program 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Orientation Program 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Photographs, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  10+ Photographs
- Private Consulting by Members of Staff, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Registration Procedures - Committee on - 1958-1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Registration Procedures - Committee on - 1958-1966 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Resident Instruction Office -- Functions, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Selective Service Class Rank for Men, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- DLA, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Labor College NYC, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Stat. Reports --Admissions OFC. 1952-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- State Univ. Reports and Questionnaires '56-'57, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- State Univ. -- Reports and Ques. 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Faculty Legislation, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Dedication, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- State Univ. --Reports and Ques. 1950-53, 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- State Univ. of N.Y. 1948-53 - Corresp., 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Student Activities Co. 1953-54 CU, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Student Attitude Survey, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Student Personnel Studies (Box 8, Folder 19)
- University Faculty Minutes - 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- University Faculty Minutes - 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- SUNY Questionnaires - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- University Faculty Minutes - '62-'65, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- University Faculty Minutes - '67-'68, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- University Faculty Minutes - '69-'70, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1968-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Student Hour Count Summaries, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Accessory Instruction - Hour Count Notices, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Accessory Instruction - General, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Student List Class Lists Spring 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists, Fall 1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists, Fall 1948 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists, Spring 1948 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Class Lists and Accessory Instr. - Fall 1949 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- IBM Class Lists - Spring 1949 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Accessory Inst. And Class Lists - Spr. '50, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Access. Inst. And Class Lists - Fall Term 1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Access. Inst. And Class - Spring 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists - Fall 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists - Spring 1952 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Accessory Instr. And Glass Lists - Fall 1952 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Summer Session 1952 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Accessory Instr. (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Accessory Instruction Fall Term 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Accessory Instruction Fall Term 1967 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Accessory Instruction Fall 1968 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Accessory Instruction -- Spring 1968 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Accessory Instruction Spring 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1962 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1962 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1963 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1963 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1964 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring 1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring 1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1960 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1961 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Accessory Instr. And Class Lists- Spring 1953 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Accessory Instr. - Class Lists - Fall 1954 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Accessory Instr. -Class Lists- Spring 1954 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring 1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Accessory Instruction - Spring Term 1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Accessory Instruction - Fall Term 1957 (Box 14, Folder 8)